（以下的节目有关于动物性行为 )
（小朋友建议在家长指引下观看 谢谢！）
我的意思是: 我允许我的孩子们观看
I mean, I'm letting my kids watch it,
但你或许会有着更高的要求
but you probably have higher standards.
大家好
Hello there.
我是莱恩雷诺斯
I'm Ryan Reynolds.
没错
Yeah, hmm.
就是那个莱恩雷诺斯
That Ryan Reynolds.
我是一个电影演员
I'm a film actor,
我偶尔也涉足电视
occasionally I dabble in television
以及其它行业
and other industries.
同样我是一位父亲
I'm also a father.
不过我已准备好放下这一切了
But I'm ready to move on from all of that crap.
那么接下来涉足什么？
So what's next?
野生动物世界  就是这个
Wildlife, that's what.
不  绝不是那种夜郎自大的家伙
Nope, not these blowhards.
它们无须我的帮助
They don't need my help.
我是冲着这群家伙来的
I'm here for these guys.
它们皆是自然界中的替补队员
Nature's benchwarmers.
我所说的顶级怪兽
I'm talking grade-A freaks
它们的生活方式怪诞不经 超乎你的想象
and their freakin' bizarre, weird, freakshow lives.
下面让我们迎接那些隐秘的动物英雄们吧
Get ready for the Underdogs.
∮ 我想成为你隐秘的动物英雄 ∮
∮ I wanna be your underdog ∮
这些家伙简直是最恶心 最怪异的动物了
These guys are the grossest, weirdest...
∮ 我不是食物链的顶级兽 可我独一无二 ∮
∮ I'm not number one, but I'm second to none ∮
它们是生命这部伟大电影中最不寻常的明星
...the most unlikely stars in the great movie of life.
∮ 英雄被过誉了  当个亡命之徒才更带劲 ∮
∮ Heroes are overrated when you are the outlaw ∮
现在是该它们大显身手的时刻
Now it's their time to shine.
∮ 因为我想成为你隐秘的动物英雄 ∮
∮ Cuz I wanna be your underdog ∮
生活中只要哪里有明目张胆的恶作剧...
Wherever there is blatant mischief,
哪里有可怜的怯懦行为...
wherever there is abject cowardice,
哪里有.. 难以描述的那个
wherever there is unbearable sexual tension...
那里就有隐秘的动物英雄
that's where you'll find the underdogs.
（让他们听见你的声音--青葱岁月）
You tell 'em, Green Day.
∮ 我不是失败者  我不是失败者 ∮
∮ I'm not a loser ∮∮ I'm not a loser ∮
∮ 我想成为你隐秘的动物英雄 ∮
∮ I wanna be your underdog ∮
我是莱恩雷诺斯
I'm Ryan Reynolds.
∮ 我想成为你隐秘的动物英雄 ∮
∮ I wanna be your underdog ∮
这里我要为这些怪咖们点赞
And I endorse these weirdoes.
《隐 秘的动 物英 雄》
有些自然规律是毋庸置疑的
Some laws of nature are incontrovertible.
其中一个重要需求就是繁衍后代
And one of the big ones is the need to reproduce.
否则就不会有动物小宝宝
Or there'd be no more itty-bitty baby animals.
关于性的问题――真的.. 我该从何说起？
The trouble with sex--and really, where do I begin?
毕竟那是1+1等于几的事
--is that you can't do it alone.
天机不可泄露
No comment.
所以 第一步是选择你的伴侣
So the first step is choosing your partner,
无论你是食物链的顶级兽...
and that's true whether you're an A-list animal,
..还是最底层的小蹦Q 都得照办
or one of the underdogs.
这是鬣狗――
This is Happy...
欢喜
...the hyena.
他或许是非洲最丑陋 最不讨喜的动物之一
He may be one of the ugliest outcasts in Africa,
但别为他感到难过
but don't feel sorry for him.
他今天过得非常愉快
He's having the best day.
先来晨跑一圈
Morning run.
∮ 是啊  对的 ∮
∮ Yeah, yeah ∮
再来一点仰卧起坐
A little self-care.
∮ 我曾经以为你可能会爱我 ∮
∮ I used to think maybe you loved me ∮
∮ 现在 宝贝 我确信 ∮
∮ Now, baby, I'm sure ∮
巴里？ 别挡住欢喜哥  继续前进吧
Not your episode, Barry. Keep moving.
最后补充点饼干
A nice snack.
∮ 我非常盼望那一天的到来 ∮
∮ And I just can't wait till the day ∮
∮ 当你来敲门时 ∮
∮ When you knock on my door ∮
简直快乐过神仙
Life couldn't get any better than this.
∮ 我沐浴在阳光下~哇..哦 ∮
∮ I'm walking on sunshine, wooah ∮
或者它也行？
Or could it?
就像参加学校舞会时荷尔蒙旺盛的中学生
Like a hormonal teenager at a middle school dance,
欢喜现在有一种想找女友的
Happy has a new and irrepressible urge
难以抑制的强烈欲望
to find a girlfriend.
但这谈何容易...
But that's not easy...
...尤其女孩子像这样的时候
...when these are the girls.
鬣狗简直把女权发挥到极致
Hyenas take female empowerment to the maximum.
他们好斗且强势
They're aggressive, dominant,
天生就是鬣狗界的女王
and automatically outrank all males.
如果这还不够吓人的话
And if that's not intimidating enough,
他们还有那个...
they also have these.
马赛克...说起来挺有趣
Pseudo-penises. That's fun to say.
巨大的女性生殖器官
Giant female genitalia.
它们是用来排尿的――很正常――
They're for peeing--standard--
还有分娩――哎哟――
giving birth--ouchie--
这让雄性鬣狗难以配合
and making mating difficult for males.
运气不佳...小子
Tough break, fella.
就初恋而言 还真不是胆小者能应付
As first loves go, they're not for the faint of heart.
但欢喜是个乐观主义者
But Happy is an optimist.
他刚刚爱上...
And he's just fallen in love...
一位真正婀娜多姿的 楚楚动人的 风华绝代的
――石榴姐
...with a stone-cold knockout.
也许他应该大胆出击
Maybe he should just ask her out.
他不算最大  但也不小了
He's a six, maybe six and a half?
他可以给她展示她喜爱的所有有趣的东西
You know, he could show her all the fun stuff he likes.
也许他们可以一起做这件事
Maybe they could do it together.
有趣的事.. 不是那个.. 对
The fun stuff, not the--yeah.
欢喜对于谈对象方面可是个菜鸟
Happy knows nothing about relationships.
但正如所有自尊心强的雄性一样
But like any self-respecting male,
他不会因为无知而放弃
he's not gonna let ignorance hold him back
表达自己的想法
from taking his shot.
正如搏一搏单车也许换摩托
坚决执行"快准狠"的战略决策
Ready, shoot, aim is what I say.
但当你缺乏经验时  往往只能失败告终
In case you don't speak hyena, that's a no.
"不行"就是明确答案
And no is a complete sentence.
当你有嘿咻的需求时
When it comes to the need to go to funky town,
你不能跳过前戏...直接进入主题
you can't skip straight to the end.
你就是...就你调皮
You just, you just can't.
你必须了解规则并付诸努力与行动
You have to learn the rules and put in the work.
不过...当务之急
Though, first things first,
你得先想办法吸引目光
you need to attract their attention.
与那些色彩艳丽的表亲相比
Unlike some of their more colorful cousins,
园丁鸟光有漂亮的外表
bowerbirds can't rely on plumage alone
是无法吸引目光的
to draw attention to themselves,
所以雄性园丁鸟一生都在努力完善
so males spend their whole lives compensating;
这对于所有雄性物种而言似乎深谙其道
painfully familiar to males of all species.
这些家伙会搭建奢华的单身公寓
These guys, they build extravagant bachelor pads,
也就人们常说的凉亭
known as bowers,
这样的凉亭随处可见
有时出现在一些人迹罕至的地方
all over town, sometimes in truly underdog locations.
如果这还不够吸引的话
And if that wasn't sad enough,
这些痴迷的单身汉还会在凉亭周围
these deluded loners surround these bowers
摆满他们精心收集的各种五颜六色的小饰品
with obsessively collected colorful knickknacks,
希望能打动潜在的对象
in the hope of impressing a potential girlfriend.
但总有这么一个家伙把一桩好事搞砸
But there's always that one guy who takes a good idea too far.
这只名叫塞巴斯蒂安的园丁鸟精心挑选了361件
And Sebastian here has meticulously curated 361 items
精美的垃圾物品...希望借此吸引到一位伴侣
of colorful trash in the hope it will win him a mate.
祝你好运  塞巴斯蒂安
Good luck, Sebastian.
这是他耗费大半生才完成的一套作品
It's a collection that's taken most of his adult life.
但对他来说这一切都是值得的
But it will all be worth it,
假如搭建的凉亭越完美
if it's good enough to dazzle a female...
那它吸引雌鸟与它交配的机会越大
...into sticking around long enough to mate with him.
到目前为止  这远远不够吸引
So far, it's not been enough.
但塞巴斯蒂安早有打算
But Sebastian has a solution.
他知道这套作品的美中不足
Rather than admit that he might be the problem,
所以他决定继续扩大自己的收藏品
he's decided to expand his collection.
最好的办法就是直接偷取别人的
And the best way to do that is to steal from someone else's.
但该选哪一样呢？
But what to choose?
一眼选中！
Bingo!
趁着对手不在家...
And while he's at his rival's place...
他觉得顺便搞点肆无忌惮的破坏也未尝不可
He figures he could try just a teeny bit of wanton vandalism.
塞巴斯蒂安  好你个坏家伙
Sebastian, you small-minded.
返回家中 他把362号物品添加到他的收藏品中
Back home, he adds item 362 to his collection.
雌鸟终于出现了
And when a female finally comes along,
希望这个新添的东西给他带来意想不到的收获
he's hoping this new addition will make all the difference.
雌鸟准备好了
She's ready.
现在塞巴斯蒂安开始集中精力
All Sebastian needs is to stay focused
给她展示值得她留下来的东西
and show her something worth sticking around for.
现在 集中注意力
Now, focus.
这是雌鸟最欢喜的吗？
What will she like best?
不是
Nope.
这个呢？
What about this?
不是.. 我开玩笑的
No, I was kidding.
好吧...这个怎样？
Okay, uh, this thing?
不...你说得对...这烂透了
No, you're right, that's terrible.
不.. 怎么会
No, definitely not.
我都不知道那是谁的
I don't even know who that belongs to.
好吧...是时候使出杀手锏了
Okay, time for the showstopper.
这是他的稀世珍宝
The finest thing he owns in the world.
当然 这相当于园丁鸟在第一次
Sure, it's the bowerbird equivalent
约会时大喊“爱老虎油！”
of screaming "I love you!" on a first date,
又或许“如果我们在一起，你会一直和我妈妈竞争...”
or "You'll always compete with my mother if we..."
无论如何 他还得试试
Anyway, she's gonna go for it.
即便这样
Or maybe not.
好的...别担心...塞巴斯蒂安
Nah, don't worry, Sebastian.
幸好你的单身公寓还在...
Who needs a mate?
..还有互联网
When you have a man cave...
还要什么自行车呢？
and the Internet.
无论你用什么办法去吸引潜在的伴侣
However you try to impress a potential partner,
了解对方的需求总是好主意
it's always a good idea to know your audience.
但请注意
But be warned.
不管你认为自己有什么优点
Whatever you think you've got going for you,
女性通常寻求的是截然不同的东西
women are usually looking for something completely different.
这是小鼻子
This is Littlenose.
这绰号有点讽刺
Kind of an ironic nickname.
她是一只长鼻猴
She's a proboscis monkey.
她经常和一群姐妹以及闺蜜
She hangs out with a bunch of sisters, girlfriends,
还有泛泛之交聚在一起
组成一个充满欢乐的女性团体
and loose acquaintances in one big, happy girl group.
加上这家伙
Plus this guy.
我现在知道她为何叫小鼻子了
Oh, I get why she's called Littlenose now.
她所有的闺蜜都有宝宝了
All her gal pals have babies.
可爱的小家伙
Cute ones.
她决定是时候为自己生个宝宝了
She's decided that it's time to have one of her own.
也就是说是时候打开交友软件
去寻找自己的理想伴侣
Which means it's time to hit the apps and find Mr. Right.
他一定就在那里...某个角落
He must be out there...somewhere.
小鼻子的一天和平日里没啥特别
Littlenose's day starts, well, like every other day,
还是从寻找食物开始
with the search for food.
老叶子都含有毒素
Mature leaves are all poisonous,
这意味着她需要去些寻找新鲜的嫩芽
and that means looking for tender young shoots
那些致死的可能性相对低一些
that are slightly less likely to kill you.
她今天的日程安排相比以往来得有趣
But today, her schedule's about to get a little more exciting.
她的寻爱消息不胫而走
Word's got out that she's looking for love.
当地的单身汉们信心十足 跃跃欲试
And the local bachelor pack are pretty confident
他们正好能满足她的需求
they've got just the thing she's looking for.
来认识一下1号单身汉吧
Meet bachelor number one.
他喜欢爵士乐 散步以及浪漫之夜
He enjoys jazz, long walks, and romantic nights in.
嗯哼 那是必须
Uh-huh, sure he does.
她宁愿吃有毒的叶子
She'd rather eat the poisonous leaves.
这是2号单身汉
Introducing bachelor number two.
一位肌肉型帅哥
A muscular bombshell,
他想凭借自己出色的运动天赋彻底征服她
he's hoping to impress her with his athletic prowess.
先洗个枣
Oh, no!
正如他是位出色的运动健将
区区鳄鱼算得了什么 对吧？
He can just walk that off, right?
来呀  放马过来吧
No, maybe not.
问题是 尽管这群年轻力壮的单身汉
Trouble is, for all their conventional qualities,
具备优良的基因和条件  可惜他们缺乏小鼻子...
these youthful, vigorous males don't possess
..所追求的那种特殊品质
the special something Littlenose is looking for.
但如果她拒绝了所有的单身汉...
But when you've rejected all the bachelors,
..还能去哪找对象呢？
where's left to look?
不行...那绝不行
Nope, no, definitely not.
好吧 这家伙老得可以当她爷爷了
Okay, he's old enough to be her grandpa.
明显牙齿都快掉光了
He's clearly behind on dental hygiene,
这早晚会给生活带来麻烦
that's gonna come back to haunt you.
但这不算糟的...更糟的是他还有...
But you know what's gonna come back to haunt you even worse?
..皮疹
The rash.
这种是传染病――很快就会蔓延至全身
That's contag--you're gonna have that all over the place.
但的身上有着某种独特的特质
But there is something about him,
而实际上这种特质
and it turns out it's exactly the thing
正是她一直所寻找的
she's been looking for.
一个跳动的...超出比例的...真真正正巨大的――
A throbbing, off-the-scales, truly enormous...
鼻子
nose.
在长鼻猴的世界里
And in the proboscis world,
这代表着他身上有着一个非常显著的特征――
that's a sign of one very specific detail--
更大的蛋量
bigger cojones.
皇室珠宝
Crown jewels.
小伙子  我喜欢这个――生动有趣的譬如
Little lads. I like that one.
或许像科学家们坚持要我说的――无赖分子
Or as the scientists insist I say, smooth criminals.
不...抱歉...是睾丸...睾丸...睾丸
No, sorry, testicles, testicles, testicles.
这意味着和他渡过一段浪漫时光
Which means a little quality time with him
就让她获得怀孕的最好机会
is her best chance
就是科学家所说的“搞大肚子”
of getting what I believe those scientists call "knocked up."
当然 贵为一方国王的他拥有4妻8妾
Sure, he may already have mated with four besties,
16嫔妃以及佳丽3千也未尝不可能
eight girlfriends, 16 neighbors,
呃对了...外加一个哪个谁谁的奶奶
uh, and someone's grandma...
当然这些女士们未必都会看走眼
But all those ladies can't be wrong.
祝你们下次好运...单身汉们！
Better luck next time, bachelors.
实际上...没有大鼻子...获胜的机会等同为零
Truth is, without the nose, you never stood a chance.
由此看出...不得不说...
Turns out, hate to say it,
"产品质量"才是王道
size does matter.
老不死的
Damn it.
但爱并不总是那么肤浅
But love isn't always that shallow.
有时候重要的并不是你拥有了什么
Sometimes it's not what you've got
而是你如何利用所拥有的东西
but what you do with it that counts.
策略决定一切
Strategy is everything.
还记得这只鬣狗"欢喜"吗？
Remember Happy?
他仔细地考虑了自己的处境
He's had a long, hard look at his situation,
突然心生一计
and he's had an idea.
当他意识到无法赢得比他更高大
With no other way to win the heart of a female
比他更有地位的雌性鬣狗的青睐时
that outsizes and outranks him,
他决定无时无刻地跟着她
he's decided he's simply gonna follow her for as long as it takes,
也许是永远
maybe forever.
在人类的社会中 像这种程度的执着
In the human world, this level of persistence
可能让你收到一分限制令
would land you a restraining order,
并让你在牢里呆个几年
uh, and two, possibly four years in prison.
更不用说这会让你变成十足的变态
To say nothing of the fact that it makes you a super creep.
不过这对于鬣狗而言 是一种久经考验的方式
But for hyenas, it's a tried and tested way
来表达它们的忠诚
to demonstrate your total devotion.
祝你好运，伙计！
Good luck with that, buddy.
你已经选定了对象
So you've chosen the one
并想出一个万无一失的策略来赢得她的芳心
and come up with a surefire strategy to win their heart,
但外面的竞争依然激烈
but it's still a crowded arena out there.
接下来的阶段是抵御竞争者
The next stage is to fend off the competition.
（κ郑
这只雄性火鸡正在求偶
This male turkey is looking for a mate.
尽管其外表看起来不并不起眼
And despite having a deeply underdog appearance,
他性感的舞姿仍然吸引了一些雌性火鸡
his sexy shimmying has still attracted some females.
他只需要通过展示他最亮眼的特色
He just needs to close the deal
就能达成交易
by flopping out his most dazzling feature.
他的冠垂
His snood.
皱巴巴的
That's wrinkly.
像一个悬垂的可伸缩的...
Like a dangly, extendable...
鼻套
nose sock.
通常情况下我不喜欢注射疗法
I'm not for injectables, typically,
不过你懂的你或许可以对那玩意
but you know, you could probably get some work done
做些整形手术
on that thing.
令人惊讶的是 就这么轻松就搞定了
Astonishingly, that's all it takes.
雌火鸡躺下...示意她已经准备好了
And the turk-lady lies down to signal she's ready.
一切计划都很顺利 简直完美
It's all going perfectly to plan.
直到...
Until...
杀出一群“程咬金”
Sock-blocked.
而且都是自己的哥们
And by his own brothers.
推土机
Bonecrusher.
浴血者
Bloodbather.
还有...伊恩
And... Ian.
噢...重翅一击！
Oooh, wing slap!
他们曾是室友
Once they were nestmates,
但现在爱情让他们成了死对头
but now love has made them bitter rivals.
在火鸡的世界里
只有一只雄火鸡可以繁殖
In turkey world, only one male can breed,
而他们的兄弟正被伊恩打得屁滚尿流
and our guy is getting his ass handed to him by Ian.
从此...伊恩成为了这里的霸主
From now on, Ian will be the sole headliner.
而其他的雄火鸡都沦为了伊恩的手下
并在他的卡拉歌舞厅工作
And all the other males will be the sad backup dancers
从那以后...他们都将默默无闻地度过余生
that no one remembers, for the rest of time,
因为他们在娱乐界中不再是惜日的香饽饽
because the entertainment industry has failed
再没有人欣赏他们的技艺
他们的付出也无法得到应有的回报
to honor their craft properly.
尽管他们依旧卖力地跳着摇摆舞
So, although he still gets to shimmy,
但他们挥动翅膀来吸引更多的雌火鸡
he'll be shaking his feathers to attract more females
只是为了供伊恩交配
for Ian to mate with.
谁让他们是“小弟”呢
A literal wingman.
但这一套对于伊恩的女友行得通吗？
But surely it doesn't apply to his girlfriend?
也许她还是会和他交配
Maybe she'll still mate with him.
她喜欢他的大鼻子
She liked his snood.
不 她更像那种让你“心碎”的女孩
Nope, she's more of a "rip your heart out" kinda gal.
伊恩..别冲动...你下来 !
Yeah, you, Ian!
好吧..火鸡小弟甘拜下风...你永远是――
霸王火鸡
Yeah, you forever.
感恩节看起来越来越有趣了
Thanksgiving is starting to look pretty damn good.
（感恩节，火鸡食谱）
（烤箱预热至一百八十度
填塞和搓揉，烹调三小r十五分钟）
（定期浇油汁，伊恩需要越久口感更佳更美味 ）
即使当爱似乎遥不可及 毫无希望时
Even when love seems hopelessly out of reach,
你也绝不能对此失去信心
you should never lose faith,
因为总会新的希望
because there's always another day.
来见识下迄今为止最肥胖的“隐秘英雄”吧
Meet our blubberiest underdog yet,
一头年轻的雄性象海豹
a young male elephant seal.
他想要繁殖后代
并且幸福来得太突然 刹那之间在眼前
He's hoping to breed and has just spotted an opportunity.
但他遇到一点小麻烦
But he's hit a little snag.
噢...卖葛！
Oh-ho-ho-ho!
一头近4000磅裸奔狂怒公象海豹
4,000 pounds of naked fury
刚刚发现了这小子企图与他的女友发生关系
who just caught him trying to mate with his girlfriend.
有没似曾相识的感觉？
Been there.
不...不  快跑...
No, no, no, no! Run, run! Run!
你死定了...愿主打救你...阿门！
Oh, you're so dead, oh, my god, you're so dead.
这小伙估计接下来要被揍得体无完肤
Our little runt is about to get the beating of his life
而这都是因爱惹的祸
and all for the sake of love.
值得么？
Is it worth it?
欲知后事如何？请看下回分解...
Keep watching.
∮ 我摔倒了  我感到疼痛  然后爬起来  我又坐好了 ∮
∮ Me caí, me paré, caminé, me subí ∮
∮ 我逆流而上  结果还是迷路了 ∮
∮ Me fui contra la corriente y también me perdí ∮
∮ 我发现自己  生活和学习  都很失败 ∮
∮ Fracasé, me encontré, lo viví y aprendí ∮
一年一度的狂欢会
都会有一群欲望的雄性象海豹
Once a year, eager male elephant seals
纷纷抵达加利福尼亚海岸
approach the shores of California
他们的目的很纯粹――交配
with one thing in mind--mating.
而海滩上聚集了数百头雌性象海豹
And with hundreds of females on the beach,
由此看来他们的机会一定很大  对吧？
the odds are pretty good, right?
不过有一个麻烦
But there's a problem.
众所周知
Come on, you saw that coming.
他们必须先通过
They've gotta get past...
海滩霸主这一关
the beachmaster.
我向你们保证这是科学术语
I promise you that's the scientific term,
也是我妈的绰号
and the nickname for my mom
当我试图偷偷溜回房子的时候
（妈...我知错了...我再也不敢了）
when I was trying to sneak back into the house.
好吧  我们言归正转
Okay, moving on.
他是这片海滩上最庞大的雄性象海豹
He's the largest male in the area.
就像一头重达两吨且脾气火爆的控制狂
Two tons of unrepressed anger and control issues.
他会把任何试图与崇拜他的女粉丝们
He'll beat the crap out of anyone
交配的家伙打得落花流水
who tries to mate with his fanbase of adoring females.
这些雌性象海豹也充当着他的线眼
Those females also act like security,
一旦发现有闯入者她们就会向这位巨无霸报告
alerting the big guy to any intruders.
但有些雌性象海豹所追求的不单是魁梧雄壮的对象
But some females are looking for more than just a beefcake.
她们还会选择体型较小  性格温和的类型
They'll go for smaller, sensitive sorts,
比如我们这只家伙
like our guy.
但他需要选择一个恰当的时机
But he's gonna need to pick the perfect moment.
那些生育能力强的雌性象海豹
The fertile females are the ones
通常位于豹群中间
in the middle of the colony.
如何偷偷绕过守卫...背着海滩霸主
The challenge is try to sneak past the guards
与一位愿意的雌性象海豹发生关系是眼前的考验
and mate with a willing partner behind the beachmaster's back.
就在这个时候...机会来了
It's not long before he sees his opening.
2号海滩霸主威武亮相
The arrival of a second beachmaster.
慢着...2号海滩霸主？
Wait, a second beachmaster?
这正是我们"隐秘动物英雄"所需要的机会
And that gives Mr. Underdog just what he needs.
一个调虎离山的机会
A diversion.
趁那些当线眼的雌性象海豹们正盯着
While the tattletales have their eyes
巨无霸沙滩大战的时候
on the big boy beach fight...
我们的主人公选定了安全暗号和安全路线
...our guy picks both a safe word
直奔生育能力强的雌性象海豹而来
and a safe route toward the fertile females.
提醒一下 安全暗号是：南瓜香料
By the way, the safe word is pumpkin spice.
他的时间不多
He won't have long.
但他不需要太多的时间
He doesn't need long.
突然...响起了警报...
Oh, there goes the alarm,
..沙滩霸主回来了...龟孙子怕是要挨一顿暴揍
and son of a beachmaster, here comes the beating.
南瓜香料...南瓜香料 麽尼麽尼空
Pumpkin spice, pumpkin spice, pumpkin spice.
一切回到了原点
Right back to where we started.
事实证明  在他被抓到之前
But it turns out he had just enough time
他有足够的时间来完成这项任务
to get the job done before he was caught.
∮ 现在 当务之急是解决问题 ∮
∮ Y no te preocupes si no ∮
那么 这样的惩罚值得吗？
So is the punishment worth it?
∮ 当你受到批评时 ∮
∮ Cuando te critiquen tú ∮
当然的！还用问吗？
Well, you bet it is.
没有谁比欢喜更懂得为爱疯狂
No one knows more about suffering for love than Happy,
这只无药可救的忠诚鬣狗
the hopelessly devoted hyena.
这就是他的梦中情人
There's the woman of his dreams.
但欢喜在哪呢？
But where's Happy?
他终于做了点自我反省
Has he finally done just a skosh of internal work,
意识到自身的价值 也稍有点尊严了吗？
realized his own self-worth, and developed a little dignity?
不...他是雄性...而且他喜欢这个计划
No, he's a male, and he likes this plan.
虽然有些动物专注于寻找唯一的对象
But while some focus on finding the one,
但并非所有动物都是这样
not everybody stops at one.
有些动物则倾向于保持更多的选择余地
Some animals prefer to keep their options wide open.
欢迎来到印度的马杜赖
Welcome to Madurai, India.
这个看似平凡的地方
The unlikely home of the darkest detective
却是漫威宇宙中黑暗侦探――
in the DC Universe...
果蝠的家园
...the fruit bat.
当然.. 这名字听起来不是很厉害.. 是的
Not the toughest name, of course, yeah.
但你知道谁才算厉害？
But you know who is tough?
蝙蝠侠？... 不是   慢着...抱歉
Bruce Wa--no? Hold on, I'm sorry,
有人认为是芭芭拉
they're telling me that it's Barbara,
芭芭拉才是――名副其实的厉害角色
Barbara's the--that actually makes a lot more sense.
芭芭拉
Barbara.
那么 芭布丝 你来猜猜看
So riddle me this, Babs.
谁会成为你的性伴侣
Who's gonna be your sexual sidekick?
在众多符合条件的雄性果蝠中
Out of the many eligible male fruit bats,
哪一只够勇敢
which one will be brave enough,
够大胆
bold enough
能成为下一代的父亲...
to be the father of...
好吧...这没礼貌了
And that is gross.
我很抱歉...芭芭拉...那...呃
I'm so sorry, Barbara, that, um...
对...这是正常反应
Yeah, that's the right reaction.
只是...这完全是个危险警报
Just, that's a total red flag.
亮红灯――那家伙到底上了多少黑名单？
Red fl--how many watchlists is that guy on?
真的是...对
啊...我的天
That's, yeah. Uh, my lord.
继续吧
Moving on.
有一张新面孔进入了芭芭的视野
Someone new just appeared on Barbara's radar.
好吧  他不是你见过的
Okay, he's not the most impressive, uh, specimen
最令人印象深刻的蝙蝠侠
of bat-manhood you've ever seen,
但令人高兴的是
but let's just be happy
芭芭拉似乎找到了她的伴侣
that Barbara seems to have found her mate.
就像大多数情侣关系一样  这有点混乱
Like most relationships, it's kind of messy,
但也许这正是一段美好故事的开始
but maybe this is the start of something really beautiful.
哦...不...他走了
Uh, nope, yeah, he's gone.
我与我父亲相处的时间都比那长
I knew my dad longer than that.
但事实证明
But it turns out Barbara the fruit bat
果蝠芭芭拉已经准备好马上拍续集
is ready for a sequel immediately.
她想给她的蝙蝠宝宝
She wants the best possible father
找个最好的爸爸
for her little bat babies,
所以她正在面试其他的应聘者
so she's auditioning other applicants.
而接下来这个家伙有一个巧妙的计划
And this next joker has a cunning plan
希望能在众多候选人中脱颖而出
成为下一代孩子的爸爸
for giving himself the best chance of landing the role.
他准备...
He's going to...
我该怎么说呢？他想...
How can I put this? He's gonna... ah, hmm.
他要清理蝙蝠洞穴
He's gonna clear out the bat cave.
嗯  好吧
Um, hmm.
哎呀...天啊...我当时还担心这会奇怪
Oh, my, oh, I was so afraid this was gonna be weird,
但没有...原来不是这样的...对
but no, that's, yeah.
专家认为这种舔舐行为
Experts think this licking
可以清除之前雄性残留的精子
removes the previous male's sperm.
而芭布丝完全同意
And Barb has no objections.
舔舐越久 他们的交配时间就越长
The longer he licks, the longer she'll let him mate.
这雄性蝙蝠角色只是《蝙蝠女》系列
This male is the first of many sequels
众多续集中的第一位角色
in this Batgirl's unique franchise.
一部接一部  一部又一部
One after another, after another.
“蝙蝠性别科学家”
Bat sex scientists--
这是蝙蝠界中真实存在的职业
which is a real career that you can choose--
不知道芭芭拉为什么会和这么多雄性交配
don't exactly know why Barbara mates with so many males,
但这可能是她确保
but it may be her way of ensuring
最强精子得以存活的方式
the strongest sperm succeeds.
如果这是漫威宇宙的运作方式
If that's the way things work in the DC Universe,
那我还有什么话说呢？
well, I mean, who am I to judge?
看到这里 你可能想知道是否所有的"隐秘英雄"
By now, you might be wondering if all underdog relationships
的情侣关系都是关于战斗的
are all about combat,
竞争
competition,
和令人心碎的拒绝
and soul-crushing rejection.
是的
And you would be right.
但当你最终找到
But all that pain fades
你的完美伴侣时
所有的痛苦都烟消云散
when you finally find your perfect partner.
这是一条豹纹蛞蝓
This is a leopard slug.
这些家伙是恋爱关系专家
These guys are relationship experts,
这条豹纹蛞蝓正在寻找自己的另一半
and this one right here is looking for the one.
我希望有朝一日重新开始我的生活
I would like to resume my life at some point,
所以让我们快进吧
so let's maybe speed this up.
∮ 你和我 ∮
∮ Toi et moi ∮
∮ 我喜欢这个游戏 ∮
∮ On se cache cache comme ∮
∮ 每次你和我 ∮
∮ Toi et moi chaque fois ∮
在这个迷人的法国酒窖角落里
还藏着另一条豹纹蛞蝓
Somewhere in this charming French cellar is another slug,
它同样渴望繁殖
equally eager to breed.
所以这条豹纹蛞蝓留下了一条
极具吸引力的黏液痕迹...
So this slug lays down a trail of highly alluring slime...
∮ 啊哈 你和我 ∮
∮ Ahh, toi et moi ∮
其充满了难闻的性信息素
...packed with stinky pheromones
能让其它的蛞蝓察觉并跟踪
for the other slug to detect and follow.
∮ 哦...不...不...啊哈 ∮
∮ Oooh, pas à pas, ahhh ∮
∮ 小心 ∮
∮ Attention ∮
我想它们找到了
I think they found it.
∮ 我想要的是你 ∮
∮ C'est toi que je veux ∮
嗯
Mmmm.
豹纹蛞蝓牌费洛蒙香水
Pheromones by Leopard Slug.
现在他们找到了彼此
Now that they've found each other,
是时候让事情发展更上一层楼了
it's time to take things to the next level.
它们一起沿着一英尺长的
Together they descend on a foot-long rope
自制黏液绳下降
of self-made mucus.
紧紧地缠绕在一起
Entwining their bodies to make sure that no one can leave
直到双方完全满意后才会离开
until both partners are fully satisfied.
法式热吻
Ahh, the French kiss.
慢着...不...那是
Wait, no, that's...
哦...不...不...不...这些不是
Oh, no, no, those aren't...
哦...这些不是...这些不是舌头...他们是...
Oh, those aren't, those aren't tongues, they're--ohhhhh.
这些是...这些是生殖器
Oh, those are, those are penises.
“生殖器”？你们都是这样说的吗？
Peni? It's that what you say?
蛞蝓界...这种说法...不存在的
Is that what the slugs say?
而这就是蛞蝓界为什么能如此的平等
And that's the reason these slugs are so egalitarian.
双方都可以雌雄切换
安能辨我是雄雌？
Both partners have male and female genitalia,
双方都可以提供和接收精子
and both give and receive sperm,
双方都可以给自己的卵子受精
which they can each use to fertilize their own eggs.
然后... 对了
Then... ah, yes.
后会有期...
Au revoir.
究竟有多少次我以这种方式结束一段关系的
I can count on both hands how many times
我双手都能数得过来
I've left a relationship this exact way.
对于蛞蝓来说 这是极品燕窝
难得的美味 营养丰富一点也不会浪费
Last slug swinging gets to eat the mucus.
不了  谢谢！
No, thank you!
这就是大结局
So, there you have it.
“隐秘的动物英雄”的恋爱宝典：
带你领略其中的美好与糟糕
The underdogs' guide to navigating the good, the bad,
还有丑陋的一面
and the ugly of relationships.
同时温馨提醒  每个动物都值得拥有一点爱
And a friendly reminder that everyone deserves a little love.
除了欢喜  他的结局...
Except Happy, who's finally...
那叫一个惨字
仿佛掉进万丈深渊
Well, he's hit rock bottom.
此刻鬣狗欢喜的内心独白：
问君能有几多愁 ？
Basically doing the hyena equivalent
恰似该死雨水...打湿我帅气的头
of crying into his drink.
只是 你们懂得 我们应该花点钱
It's just, you know, I think we should just spend some money
请迈克尔・博顿帮忙
on Michael Bolton.
《没有你我该如何生活》歌曲播放中...
["How Am I Supposed to Live Without You?" plays]
就是这首...
There you go, ooh.
爽！
Mmm, that's good.
他代表着那些无法为自己发声的人
Oh, he speaks for those who can't speak for themselves.
但要说我懂点喜剧的话 其实我一点不懂
But if I know anything about rom coms, and I don't,
我只是照着桑德拉・布洛克告诉我的方法去做
I just did everything Sandra Bullock told me to do,
正是有了这些失败经历的坚实基石
it's that rock bottom is the solid foundation
才让你今后的人生越走越平顺 越来越精彩...
upon which you build true love.
而..欢喜？
And Happy?
好的...他决定再试最后一次
Well, he's gonna give it one last shot.
啊..哈  等等.. 稍等一下
H-h-hold the phone, hold on.
难道说欢喜要走狗屎运了？
Wait, could Happy's luck be turning around?
在受到数周的冷漠与无情的轻视后
After weeks of quiet, unmitigated contempt,
精诚所至金石为开 他终将迎来幸福美满的结局
造就了鬣狗界的一个凄美动人的传奇故事...
it looks like he's finally about to get his happy end--
不...这是个误导...这还不是他真正的结局
Oh, no, gonna stay away from that.
他即将得到...他该有的结局
He's gonna get his, the ending he deser--the...
他即将...
he's gonna, um,
他马上...
he's gonna.
不...他要去洗碗碟
No. He is going to get the dishes done.
我们可以这么说吗？
Can we say that?
现在雌性鬣狗开始跟着他
Now she begins to follow him.
别紧张...她应该不会要你狗命
Hold your nerve, she almost certainly won't kill you.
剩下要解决是阻碍他们快乐的"假小弟"问题
All that's left to solve is the pseudo-penis situation.
她把它像可伸缩的百叶窗一样卷回去
She does this by rolling it back
来实现这一操作
like a retractable shutter.
这有点像...
It's kind of like, um...
它就像是...怎么形容好呢？
it's like of like, uh, how do you describe it?
就像用没有手的香蕉
Like a, it's like turning a sock inside out
把袜子翻过来一样
using a banana with no hands.
所以 经过了漫长的等待...
So, after all that waiting,
当这事情真的发生时
那简直是媲美燃放绚丽的烟花场面
when it does happen, it's not exactly fireworks.
但对于欢喜来说 那就像是...
But for Happy, it's like all his birthdays
一次性过完所有生日
have come at once.
对...就像他的美梦成真...
Yeah, it's like his dreams came true,
..他那湿漉漉的美梦
his, his dreams, his... soaking wet dreams.
那么...其他动物的情况怎么样呢？
So how's everyone else doing?
塞巴斯蒂安现在已拥有1009件废物饰品
Sebastian now has 1,009 items of garbage,
但结果依然如意料之中...他还是没有女友
but still, predictably, has no girlfriend.
小鼻子终于拥有了她梦寐以求的宝宝
Littlenose has the baby that she's always dreamed of,
而且她对于现在的生活感到非常满意
and hardly misses single life at all.
伊恩从中领悟到了关于霸"业"的宝贵道理
Ian learned a valuable lesson about karma.
而我们的主角象海豹公子变得肥胖了
Our elephant seal lover boy is bulking up,
皮肤像被肤色剂喷上一般黑
getting spray-tanned,
准备成为明年的沙滩霸主...
ready to become next year's Mr. Beachmaster.
这条豹纹蛞蝓
The slugs.
还在离开中
They are still leaving.
而芭芭拉呢？
And Barbara?
她拥有自己的影艺事业
She has her own cinematic universe
包括八部续集
comprising of eight sequels,
两部重启版
还有一部宝莱坞音乐剧正在筹备中...
two reboots, and a Bollywood musical in the works.
这就是真正的蝙蝠女的巅峰时刻.....
Now that is how you release Batgirl.
字幕制作：月朗风清
GOOD LUCK FOR YOU!!